(Amy:)I just read about
an experiment designed
(Amy:)to see if you could
make two people fall
(Amy:)in love in a matter of hours.
(Leonard:)That doesn't sound right.
(Leonard:)My research has shown that
it takes three to five years
(Leonard:)of shameless begging.
(Penny:)Honey, neither of us comes off
good in that story.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Yeah, I-I...
(Raj:)I saw that article
you're talking about.
(Raj:)Uh, the participants
ask each other a series
(Raj:)of questions designed
to promote intimacy.
(Amy:)And then they finish it off
by staring
(Amy:)into each other's eyes
for four minutes.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's nonsense.
(Sheldon:)I proclaimed my
love for you.
(Sheldon:)And the last time I
looked into your eyes
(Sheldon:)was when you thought
you had conjunctivitis.
(Amy:)Other than the fact
that I had it,
(Amy:)that was a magical night.
(Penny:)Raj, would you ever try an
experiment like that with Emily?
(Raj:)What? I don't need
science to win her heart.
(Raj:)I have my family's
wealth for that.
(Leonard:)I'm telling you, you can't
create love in a few hours.
(Leonard:)Right?
Oh, careful.
(Penny:)You're poking at the whole
foundation of The Bachelor.
SHELDON:
Yeah, but
(Sheldon:)we don't have to debate this.
(Sheldon:)We're scientists.
(Sheldon:)We can conduct our own research.
Yeah, I propose that we imprison
(Sheldon:)two street people.
No.
(Amy:)And...
(Sheldon:)You didn't even let me finish.
Forget it!
Oh!
(Sheldon:)So, you can experiment
on all the apes you want.
(Sheldon:)But I want to manipulate
the emotions of two captive
(Sheldon:)human beings, suddenly
I'm the monster.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Why don't you
(Raj:)just do the test?
(Sheldon:)In the interest of science,
I'd be willing to.
(Penny:)What? You're okay with
an experiment where you have
(Penny:)to answer awkward questions
about your innermost feelings?
(Amy:)Yes.
(Penny:)Please, can I do it
with him? Please?!
(Leonard:)I've been listening
to Sheldon's feelings on things
(Leonard:)for ten years.
Tag, you're it.
(Raj:)Yeah, but what
if the experiment works?
(Penny:)I'm not gonna fall
in love with Sheldon.
AMY:
That's what I said.
(Amy:)Before I knew it,
he pontificated his way
(Amy:)right into my heart.
(Sheldon:)Uh, fun fact--
"pontificate"
(Sheldon:)comes from the Latin
word "pontifex,"
which means "bridge
builder" or "Pope."
(Leonard:)In love yet?